Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs, 1906-1960 and undated RL.00657
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs
1906-1960 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00657
3 Linear Feet 104 items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The JWT 35mm Microfilm Proofs collection spans the years 1906-1960 and consists primarily of images of print advertisements and proofs taken from proof books and portfolios of domestic and foreign JWT offices. Clients include Ballantine's, B.F. Goodrich, Butterick, Corning, Crowell Publishing, Davey Tree Surgeons, General Cigar, General Motors, Guinness, Horlicks, J.B. Williams, Jergens, Johns-Manville, Nash, Northam Warren, Pennsylvania RR, RCA, Sharp & Dohme, Shell, Standard Brands, Sun Maid, Swift, Sylvania, United Airlines, Ward Baking, and Welch's Grape Juice. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Historical Note
Beginning in the late 1930s, proof books containing advertisements of former clients, foreign clients and domestic clients from offices other than New York were put on microfilm. It is believed that after items were microfilmed, the originals were destroyed.
Collection Overview
The JWT 35mm Microfilm Proofs collection spans the years 1906-1960 and consists primarily of images of print advertisements and proofs taken from proof books and portfolios of domestic and foreign JWT offices. Clients include Ballantine's, B.F. Goodrich, Butterick, Corning, Crowell Publishing, Davey Tree Surgeons, General Cigar, General Motors, Guinness, Horlicks, J.B. Williams, Jergens, Johns-Manville, Nash, Northam Warren, Pennsylvania RR, RCA, Sharp & Dohme, Shell, Standard Brands, Sun Maid, Swift, Sylvania, United Airlines, Ward Baking, and Welch's Grape Juice.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged by reel number and physical sequence of images on microfilm. Items were microfilmed in several categories: general accounts, foreign office clients, western offices, and portfolios of inactive client accounts.
Related Material
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements Collection
J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection
J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices Records
Roy Lightner Collection of Antique Advertisements
Advertising; Advertising -- United States -- History; Proofs (printed matter); Advertising -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Microfilms; Corning Glass Works; Crowell Publishing Company; B.F. Goodrich Company; Butterick Publishing; Andrew Jergens Company (Cincinnati, Ohio); United Airlines; Ward Baking Company; Welch Grape Juice Company; Standard Brands Incorporated; Sun Maid Growers of California; Swift & Company; Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.; Shell Oil Company; Sharp & Dohme; Radio Corporation of America; Pennsylvania Railroad; P. Ballantine & Sons; Northam Warren Corporation; Nash Motors Company; Johns-Manville Corporation; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J.B. Williams Co; J. Walter Thompson Company; Guinness (Firm); General Motors Corporation; General Cigar Company (Philadelphia, Pa.); Davey Tree Expert Company (Kent, Ohio)
- Domestic Advertisements, 1906-1941; 1
  - Addressograph, 1914 (Film-reel 1)
  - American Appraisal Co. (factory appraisal financeial service), 1922 (Film-reel 1)
  - American Corrrespondence School of Law, 1915 (Film-reel 1)
  - Arbuckle Brothers (Ariosa, Yuban coffees), 1913-1924 (Film-reel 1)
  - Elizabeth Arden, 1923 (Film-reel 1)
  - Artloom (rugs), 1937 (Film-reel 1)
  - Associated Tile Manufacturers (Keromic tiles), 1928 (Film-reel 1)
  - Automatic Electric Co. (interoffice telephones), 1915-1917 (Film-reel 1)
  - Audit Bureau of Circulations, 1930-1933 (Film-reel 1)
  - Ballard (Oven-ready biscuits), 1931-1933 (Film-reel 1)
  - Ballard (Oven-ready biscuits), 1931-1933 (Film-reel 2)
  - A.B.A. Cheques, 1915 (Film-reel 2)
  - Belding Brothers & Co. (silks, fabric), 1908-1910 (Film-reel 2)
  - Barbours Linen Thread, 1924-1927 (Film-reel 2)
  - A. Bellor & Co. (ladies' cloaks, suits, dresses), 1920-1927 (Film-reel 2)
  - Berkey & Gay (furniture), 1917-1919 (Film-reel 2)
  - Canadian Colonial Airways, 1929-1931 (Film-reel 2)
  - Bartlett Pears, 1937 (Film-reel 2)
  - Bishopric Manufacturing Co. (building materials), 1925-1927 (Film-reel 2)
  - Bischof (ladies' clothing), 1914-1915 (Film-reel 2)
  - Paul Block (pictorial revue), 1917-1929 (Film-reel 2)
  - Bocaire (Turner and Walls men's shirts and shirting), 1921-1922 (Film-reel 2)
  - Paul Von Boeckman (physical culture), 1914 (Film-reel 2)
  - Boeing School of Aeronautics, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 2)
  - Bontex (H.B. Oaflin Co.; wash fabrics and dresses), undated (Film-reel 2)
  - Borax Soap Chips, 1917-1918 (Film-reel 2)
  - A.S. Boyle (Old English Floor Wax), 1917-1922 (Film-reel 2)
  - Brenlin Window Shades (Chaow Breneman Co.), 1915-1926 (Film-reel 2)
  - Brunswick-Balke-Collender (bowling equipment), 1940 (Film-reel 2)
  - Burry Biscuit co., 1937-1939 (Film-reel 2)
  - Butterick, 1922-1925 (Film-reel 2)
  - Butterick, 1922-1925 (Film-reel 3)
  - Carter's Underwear, 1913-1932 (Film-reel 3)
  - Edward A. Cassidy (Kimbal Auto Jacks, Casco Tire Pump, C. Piel Co., G.P. Muffler Cut-out), 1917-1920 (Film-reel 3)
  - CECO (radio tubes), 1930 (Film-reel 3)
  - Central Bank of Oakland, 1934-1935 (Film-reel 3)
  - Central Public Service Corp. (utility), 1930-1933 (Film-reel 3)
  - Chatham Manufacturing Co. (blankets, sheets, pillowcases), 1925-1940 (Film-reel 3)
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy R.R., 1925-1931 (Film-reel 3)
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy R.R., 1925-1931 (Film-reel 4)
  - Close's Pocket Candies (George Close Co.), 1920 (Film-reel 4)
  - Coast Fishing Co. (Balto dog food, Puss and Boots cat food), 1933-1936 (Film-reel 4)
  - Cofield Motor Washer (washing machines), 1914 (Film-reel 4)
  - Colgate & Co. (toilet goods), 1906-1914 (Film-reel 4)
  - Cortley Clothes (Cohen Cohn and Lang; men's clothes), 1921 (Film-reel 4)
  - C.E. Conover Co. (Naiad dress shields), 1906-1917 (Film-reel 4)
  - Cooper's (men's underwear), 1939 (Film-reel 4)
  - Continental Motor Manufacturing Co., 1914-1920 (Film-reel 4)
  - Corning Glass Works (baby bottles, kitchen utensils, laboratory equipment, Stueben glass, conaphore, auto headlight lenses), 1918- (Film-reel 4)
  - Corning Glass Works (baby bottles, kitchen utensils, laboratory equipment, Stueben glass, conaphore, auto headlight lenses), 1918- (Film-reel 5)
  - Corticelli Silk Co. (dresses, hosiery, silk thread, knitting yarns), 1924-1928 (Film-reel 5)
  - Cox Confectionary Co. (Romance chocolates), 1920-1925 (Film-reel 5)
  - Cream of Wheat, 1923-1938 (Film-reel 5)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS, WBBM radio station), undated (Film-reel 5)
  - Crosley Radio, 1929 (Film-reel 5)
  - Crowell Publishing Company (American, Collier's, Farm and Fireside, Woman's Home Companion magazines), 1924-1927 (Film-reel 5)
  - Crowell Publishing Company (American, Collier's, Farm and Fireside, Woman's Home Companion magazines), 1924-1927 (Film-reel 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries Inc. (Chesebro Bros & Robbins, Inc. fish brokers, Nordic frozen fish steaks), 1929-1931 (Film-reel 6)
  - Alkalitkia Co. (drugs), 1938-1939 (Film-reel 6)
  - Curtiss Candy Co. (Baby Ruth chewing gum and candy bar, Chico peanuts), 1928-1931 (Film-reel 6)
  - Curtis Publishing Co. (Ladies Home Journal), 1931-1938 (Film-reel 6)
  - Curtis Wood Work, 1913 (Film-reel 6)
  - City Baking Co. (Mrs. Schmidt's bread), 1926 (Film-reel 6)
  - Curtis Flying Service, undated (Film-reel 6)
  - Davey Tree Surgeons, 1911-1937 (Film-reel 6)
  - Davey Tree Surgeons, 1911-1937 (Film-reel 7)
  - Curtis Wright Trade, 1929 (Film-reel 7)
  - Davey Tree Surgeons, 1911-1937 (Film-reel 7)
  - Del Ray Foods (spaghetti), 1933 (Film-reel 7)
  - Derryvale Givens (linens), 1917 (Film-reel 7)
  - Detroit Brewing Co., 1937 (Film-reel 7)
  - Diamond Crystal Salt, 1922-1925 (Film-reel 7)
  - Dictophone, 1916 (Film-reel 7)
  - Doubleday Page Co. (book publishers), 1914 (Film-reel 7)
  - Douglas Lighter (Hargraft & Co., cigarette lighters), 1926 (Film-reel 7)
  - Driecer & Co., 1926 (Film-reel 7)
  - Drakes Cakes, 1911-1916 (Film-reel 7)
  - Durham Duplex Razor Co., 1934-1938 (Film-reel 7)
  - Dwight Anchor (sheets and pillowcases), undated (Film-reel 7)
  - Easy Washing Machines, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 7)
  - Eberhard Pencil Co. (Faber, Mongol pencils, Van Dyck and Kleerit erasers), 1929-1936 (Film-reel 7)
  - Electric Boat Co. (Nelsco diesel engines, New London Ship and Engine Co., Elco cruisers), 1925-1932 (Film-reel 7)
  - Elms and Sellon (D&J Anderson Ginghams fabrics, Standish fabrics), 1923-1926 (Film-reel 7)
  - Elms and Sellon (D&J Anderson Ginghams fabrics, Standish fabrics), 1923-1926 (Film-reel 8)
  - Emerson Drug So. (Bromo-Seltzer), 1935-1940 (Film-reel 8)
  - Erskine & Dontorth (Danersk furniture), 1920-1927 (Film-reel 8)
  - Felt & Tarront Manufacturing Co. (Comptometer), 1931 (Film-reel 8)
  - Exchange Trust Co. (banking), 1908-1916; 1925-1927 (Film-reel 8)
  - Felt & Tarront Manufacturing Co. (Comptometer), 1931 (Film-reel 8)
  - Fidelio Brewery, 1933-1934 (Film-reel 8)
  - Fiske & Co. (Frisklock, Tapestry bricks), 1914-1917 (Film-reel 8)
  - Flintkote Corp. (building materials), 1934 (Film-reel 8)
  - Foamite-Childs Corp. (fire protection, firefoam), 1923-1927 (Film-reel 8)
  - Foamite-Childs Corp. (fire protection, firefoam), 1923-1927 (Film-reel 9)
  - Foremost Dairy Products Inc. (Foremost ice cream and milk), 1929-1931 (Film-reel 9)
  - Augusta Ice and Coal Co. (Allburn coal), 1929 (Film-reel 9)
  - Urm. Freihofer Baking Co. (bread), 1929- (Film-reel 9)
  - Robert Gair & Co., Inc. (package merchandising), 1920-1924 (Film-reel 9)
  - Robert Gair & Co., Inc. (Harmony, Garner fabrics), 1927-1928 (Film-reel 9)
  - Gates Tours (vacation cruises), 1921-1926 (Film-reel 9)
  - P.A. Geier Co. (Royal electric vacuum cleaner), 1921-1924 (Film-reel 9)
  - General Shoe Co. (Jorman, Fortune shoes), 1938 (Film-reel 9)
  - General Timber Service Inc. (Weyerhauser Forest Products, Balsane wool blankets, insulation division), 1926-1933 (Film-reel 10)
  - Gill Bros. (lighting fixtures), 1914-1915 (Film-reel 10)
  - Globe-Wernicke (ofice equipment), 1927 (Film-reel 10)
  - Good Luck Food Co. (Good Luck for Lemon pie filling), 1922-1926 (Film-reel 10)
  - B.F. Goodrich, 1928-1933 (Film-reel 10)
    Scope and Contents
    Rubber products; Zippers overshoes, rubber footwear and soles/heels, airplane tires, Goodrich Silvertown, Brunswick, Diamond, Cavalier, Miller, Hood automobile tires, Farren-oid fan belts, mechanical and drug sundries, Miller Rubber Products toys and etc., Celeste spray douche, Sojourn fountain syringe, Diamond rubber belts, marine equipment
  - B.F. Goodrich, 1928-1933 (Film-reel 11)
  - Graham (Graham Bradley tractor, automobiles), 1937-1939 (Film-reel 11)
  - Grand Trunk Railway Line, 1920 (Film-reel 11)
  - Griedesieck Western Brewery (Stag, Oldbrau beer), 1937-1940 (Film-reel 11)
  - Gruen Watchmakers Guild (Verithin watch), 1915-1932 (Film-reel 12)
  - Gulbransen (player pianos), 1926 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hammond Organ, 1936 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hanovia Chemical Manufacturers (Alpine sun lamp, Kromayer lamp), 1928-1930 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hall-Borchet Dress Form Co., undated (Film-reel 12)
  - Hasslers Manufacturing Co. (auto shock absorbers), 1927-1928 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hathaway Baking Co. (Dolly Madison, Dietz bread, Hathaway's bread), 1926-1934 (Film-reel 12)
  - Richard Hellmann Inc. (Hellmann's Blue Ribbon Mayonnaise), 1928 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hartsborn Shade Rollers, 1915 (Film-reel 12)
  - Peter Henderson (seeds), 1915-1926 (Film-reel 12)
  - Henriette (compacts and cigarette cases), 1937-1938 (Film-reel 12)
  - Histon Products Co. (drugs, Anatone, Jeltone), undated (Film-reel 12)
  - Wm. Hollins Co. Inc. (Viyella knitting yarns), 1932 (Film-reel 12)
  - H.P. Hood & Sons (milk), 1933 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hoosier Manufacturing Co. (kitchen cabinets), 1923-1927 (Film-reel 12)
  - Hooven-Allison Co. (Bue Heart rope), 1920-1927 (Film-reel 12)
  - Horlick's Malted Milk, 1917-1929 (Film-reel 12)
  - Horlick's Malted Milk, 1917-1929 (Film-reel 13)
  - Howlett & Hockmeyer (Waterside Corduroy suede-like ladies hats, Zip On Body clothes), 1923-1929 (Film-reel 13)
  - Richard Hudnut (cosmetics), 1929 (Film-reel 13)
  - Deauville & DuBarry (cosmetics), undated (Film-reel 13)
  - Chicago Herald & Examiner, 1928-1929 (Film-reel 13)
  - George P. Ide & Co. (shirts and collars), 1926-1927 (Film-reel 13)
  - Ideal power lawn mower, 1915 (Film-reel 13)
  - Industrial Alcohol Institute (denatured alcohol, antifreeze), 1929 (Film-reel 13)
  - Thomas P. Jeffrey Co. (automobiles), 1915 (Film-reel 13)
  - Japan Tea Promotion Committee, 1927 (Film-reel 13)
  - Jovan Corp. (importers of ginger ale), 1928 (Film-reel 13)
  - International Vitamin Corp. (IVC Pearls vitamin capsules), 1930 (Film-reel 13)
  - International Silver Co. (premium give-away), 1939 (Film-reel 13)
  - International Shoe Corp., undated (Film-reel 13)
  - Andrew Jergens Co. (Woodbury's soap, shaving stick, Jergens Violet Glycerine soap, lotion, Castolay Baby's Soap, Ben Hur perfume), 1911-1936 (Film-reel 13)
  - Andrew Jergens Co. (Woodbury's soap, shaving stick, Jergens Violet Glycerine soap, lotion, Castolay Baby's Soap, Ben Hur perfume), 1911-1936 (Film-reel 14)
  - A.C. Krum & Sons (macaroni), 1926-1928 (Film-reel 15)
  - Kops Brothers (Nemo-Flex wonderlift, Sensation Steps, Rapid Medial Belt Co. medical trusses, corsets, brassieres), 1925-1934 (Film-reel 15)
  - Klein Rapid Shoe Repair Co., 1929 (Film-reel 15)
  - Klear Flox Linen Rug Co., 1922 (Film-reel 15)
  - A&M Karaghensian (Herati rugs), 1924-1927 (Film-reel 15)
  - Johnson & Johnson (Johnson's baby powder), 1925 (Film-reel 15)
  - Jobbers's Overall Co. (Blue Buckle overalls, work clothes), 1920 (Film-reel 15)
  - La Gerardine Inc. (La Gerardine hair set, Gray Ban hair rinse, Insto-Wave hair set), 1930-1933 (Film-reel 15)
  - Lamont Corliss & Co. (Peppermint Loriots candy), 1920 (Film-reel 15)
  - Langendorf United Bakeries (California Spun Slices, Pro Perland's Wheat Bread, Old Homestead bread, Royalets cupcakes), 1922- (Film-reel 15)
  - Langendorf United Bakeries (California Spun Slices, Pro Perland's Wheat Bread, Old Homestead bread, Royalets cupcakes), 1922- (Film-reel 16)
  - Lansdowne (Schweiger, Inc., embroidery patterns, dresses), 1914-1930 (Film-reel 16)
  - Lehn & Fink (Pebeco toothpaste, Bovril beef drink, Fly-Flu exterminators), 1923-1929 (Film-reel 16)
  - Leslie Salt, 1934-1936 (Film-reel 16)
  - Lever Bros. (Lifebuoy soap, Rinso detergent), 1918-1925 (Film-reel 16)
  - J.B. Lippencott Co. (book publishers), 1911-1916 (Film-reel 17)
  - Lewis Manufacturing Co. (contractors, homes), 1916-1917 (Film-reel 17)
  - Log Cabin (syrup), 1922-1925 (Film-reel 17)
  - Lyon & Healy (musical instruments), 1919-1920 (Film-reel 17)
  - Majestic Co. (coal chutes), 1917 (Film-reel 17)
  - W.H. & A.E. Margerison & co. (Martex towels), 1927 (Film-reel 17)
  - Matson Navigation Co. (Matson Line cruises), 1929-1931 (Film-reel 17)
  - McCall Corp. (McCall's, Red Book magazines), 1932 (Film-reel 17)
  - McCawley & Co. (Slip-On children's clothing), 1924-1925 (Film-reel 17)
  - Melville Shoe Corp. (Rival, John Ward, Thom McAn men's shoes), 1925 (Film-reel 17)
  - Massachusetts Baking Co. (White Rose bread), 1922 (Film-reel 17)
  - Mennen Co. (shaving supplies), 1914-1915 (Film-reel 17)
  - Meredith Publishing Co. (Successful Living, Better Homes & Gardens magazines), 1928 (Film-reel 17)
  - Moorman Manufacturing Co. (feeds), 1928 (Film-reel 17)
  - Moorman Manufacturing Co. (feeds), 1928 (Film-reel 18)
  - Motor Improvements, Inc. (Purolator oil filters), 1926 (Film-reel 18)
  - Old Witch Co. (cleaning ammonia), 1929-1930 (Film-reel 18)
  - Olds Motor Works (Oldsmobile), 1914 (Film-reel 18)
  - Old Dominion Garment Co. (Blue Buckle overalls), undated (Film-reel 18)
  - Norwich Pharmacal Co. (Unguentine, Vagiforms, Swan shaving cream), 1924 (Film-reel 18)
  - Mountain Valley mineral water, 1940 (Film-reel 18)
  - National Lumber Promotion Comm. (Nato Lumbers Manufacturing Association co-op), 1928-1932 (Film-reel 18)
  - National Electric Cookery Council (promotion), 1932 (Film-reel 18)
  - Vanadium Corporation of America (alloys), 1940 (Film-reel 18)
  - National Bureau of Surety and Casualty Underwriters (Safe Drivers Reward Plan, casualty insurance), 1938-1939 (Film-reel 18)
  - New England Candy Co. (Necco wafers, Balsters & OK), 1927-1929 (Film-reel 18)
  - New Jersey Brewers' Association (promotion), 1938 (Film-reel 18)
  - New York Chapter of National Music Appreciation Committee, 1940 (Film-reel 18)
  - New York Post, 1940 (Film-reel 18)
  - Norfolk & Portsmouth (resort), 1924-1928 (Film-reel 18)
  - Northern Pacific Railway, 1926-1930 (Film-reel 18)
  - Northwestern Expanded Metal Co., 1914 (Film-reel 18)
  - Nash Motors Co. (Nash, Lafayette automobiles), 1934 (Film-reel 18)
  - Nash Motors Co. (Nash, Lafayette automobiles), 1934 (Film-reel 19)
  - Omar Baking Co. (bread and flour), 1937-1938 (Film-reel 19)
  - Orange Crush (soft drink), 1934 (Film-reel 19)
  - Osgood Deflection Lens (auto headlight lens), 1916 (Film-reel 19)
  - O'Sullivan Rubber Co. (rubber shoe heels), 1912-1933 (Film-reel 19)
  - Pacific Coast Electric Bureau (promotion), 1934 (Film-reel 19)
  - Peace Dale Mills (J.P. Stevens Co., knitting yarns), 1920-1922 (Film-reel 19)
  - Palisade Manufacturing Co. (Kitchen Bouquet food flavoring), 1914 (Film-reel 19)
  - Parfumerie St. Denis (bath luxuries), 1929 (Film-reel 19)
  - J. Parker Pray Inc. (Opalene nail enamel), 1926 (Film-reel 19)
  - Parker-Regan Corp. (Betty Bright floor mops), 1927-1929 (Film-reel 19)
  - Park-Lexington Corp (Grand Central Palace exhibition hall), undated (Film-reel 19)
  - Pathescope Corp. (industrial films), 1930-1934 (Film-reel 19)
  - Pin Ap'A (Lamont Corliss soft drink), 1916 (Film-reel 19)
  - J.C. Penney, 1928-1929 (Film-reel 19)
  - J.C. Penney, 1928-1929 (Film-reel 20)
  - Pineapple Producers Cooperative Association (promotion), 1933 (Film-reel 20)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (Film-reel 20)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (Film-reel 21)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (Film-reel 22)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (Film-reel 23)
  - Pennsylvania Rubber Co. (tires, golf balls, tennis balls, etc.), 1928 (Film-reel 23)
  - Permutit Co. (water softener), 1930-1931 (Film-reel 23)
  - Peter Kailler Kohler (Lamont Corliss, Peter's chocolate and cocoa, Redges, Nestle), 1919 (Film-reel 23)
  - Peter Kailler Kohler (Lamont Corliss, Peter's chocolate and cocoa, Redges, Nestle), 1919 (Film-reel 24)
  - Phoenix Hosiery (men's and women's), 1932-1934 (Film-reel 24)
  - E.A. Pierce & Co. (The Lansdowne Co.), 1930 (Film-reel 24)
  - Permutit Co. (water softener), 1932-1933 (Film-reel 24)
  - Piggly Wiggly Stores, 1927 (Film-reel 24)
  - Ed. Pinand (Eau de Quinine, Lilac Vegetal, toiletries_, 1926-1929 (Film-reel 24)
  - Pope Manufacturing Co. (motorcycles), 1914 (Film-reel 24)
  - Franklin Baker Co. Inc. (coconut), 1925-1929 (Film-reel 24)
  - Cheek Neal Coffee Co. (Maxwell House), 1925- (Film-reel 24)
  - Cheek Neal Coffee Co. (Maxwell House), 1925- (Film-reel 25)
  - Douglas Pectin Corp. (Certo), 1928 (Film-reel 25)
  - Postum Cereal Co. (Grape-Nuts), 1924 (Film-reel 25)
  - President Suspenders, 1924-1929 (Film-reel 25)
  - Florida Citrus Exchange (Florigold oranges), 1937 (Film-reel 25)
  - Rowntree & Co. (Chu-Fru candies), 1925 (Film-reel 25)
  - Roosevelt Hotel, 1938 (Film-reel 25)
  - Roma Wine Co. (Roma, La Boheme wines), 1935 (Film-reel 25)
  - Richardson Co. (roofing), 1923 (Film-reel 25)
  - Republic Rubber Co. (tires), 1915 (Film-reel 25)
  - Reo Truck Co., 1914 (Film-reel 25)
  - Relaince Property Management (Ritz-Carlton Atlantic City), 1932 (Film-reel 25)
  - Red Cross Shoes (ladies' shoes), 1912-1922 (Film-reel 25)
  - Reckitts Ltd. (bath perfume), 1930 (Film-reel 25)
  - Realsilk (men's and women's hose), 1931 (Film-reel 25)
  - Rayon Institute of America, Inc. (rayon promotion), 1929-1930 (Film-reel 25)
  - Red Head spark plug, 1918 (Film-reel 25)
  - Rand McNally & Co. (maps, Child Life magazine), 1925 (Film-reel 25)
  - Rand McNally & Co. (maps, Child Life magazine), 1925 (Film-reel 26)
  - Quaker Oats Co. (Quaker Oats cereal, Aunt Jemima, Muffets cereal, macaroni), 1924-1936 (Film-reel 26)
  - Gorham Co. (hotel, household, ecclesiastical silverware, Spaulding Gorham, Black-Starr, Frost Gorham), 1929-1932 (Film-reel 26)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast), 1920-1922 (Film-reel 26)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast), 1922-1929 (Film-reel 27)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast), 1929-1933 (Film-reel 28)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast; Life Begins at Forty 1937: see also reel 50), 1933-1938 (Film-reel 29)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast; Life Begins at Forty 1937: see also reel 50), 1933-1938 (Film-reel 30)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Royal Baking Powder), 1923-1932 (Film-reel 30)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Royal Baking Powder, gelatine, pudding), 1925-1938 (Film-reel 31)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Royal Baking Powder, gelatine, pudding, desserts, mayonnaise, Fleischmann's Gin), 1934-1940 (Film-reel 32)
  - Sardine Fisheries of Maine (Maine sardines), 1930 (Film-reel 32)
  - Savage Arms Corporation (Savage Stevens guns), 1923 (Film-reel 32)
  - Savage Washer & Dryer (washing machines), 1923 (Film-reel 32)
  - F. Schumacher & Co. (fabrics), 1922-1929 (Film-reel 32)
  - F. Schumacher & Co. (fabrics), 1929-1930 (Film-reel 33)
  - Seabord Rice Milling Co. (Comet rice), 1917 (Film-reel 33)
  - Shults Bread Co., 1922-1923 (Film-reel 33)
  - Sealcones Inc. (containers), 1931 (Film-reel 33)
  - Seamless Rubber Co. (Surgeon's gloves, sporting goods, 1934-1940 (Film-reel 33)
  - Lewis Searing Co. (grease cups and cartridges), 1920 (Film-reel 33)
  - Seeck & Kade (Persussin, Actin), 1931-1941 (Film-reel 33)
  - Senrico Toothpaste Co., 1919 (Film-reel 33)
  - Silk Association of America (promotion), 1916-1921 (Film-reel 33)
  - R.F. Simmons Co. (chains), 1913-1920 (Film-reel 33)
  - Simmons Co. (beds and mattresses), 1927-1928 (Film-reel 33)
  - Simmons Co. (beds and mattresses), 1927-1928 (Film-reel 34)
  - L.C. Smith and Corona Typewriters, Inc., 1930-1932 (Film-reel 34)
  - Simmons Co. (mattresses, coil springs, metal beds, studio couches, Beautyrest mattresses), 1932-1938 (Film-reel 34)
  - Smokador Manufacturing Co. Inc. (smoke stands), 1928-1929 (Film-reel 34)
  - Sonotone Corp. (hearing aids), 1930-1931 (Film-reel 34)
  - Sonotone Corp. (hearing aids), 1930-1931 (Film-reel 35)
  - Spaulding & Merrick (tobacco), undated (Film-reel 35)
  - Stanley Insulating Co. (vacuum bottles), 1918-1928 (Film-reel 35)
  - Sterling Varnish Co. (Nitrex automotive tire coating), 1920 (Film-reel 35)